Okay, there we go.
好了   这就行了
It won't be long before a rescue plane sees our SOS
很快救生飞机就会发现我们
and flies us back to civilization.
带我们飞回文明世界
I don't hear any planes.
我没看到有飞机
Or helicopters.
或是直升机
Maybe Dave is coming in a hot-air balloon.
也许戴夫会坐着热气球来
Cause those things are really quiet.
那个没有声音
-I don't think Dave is gonna be in a hot-air balloon.-But
-我想戴夫弄不到热气球 -但是
-he is coming, right?-Of course he is.
-他会来的   对吗 -那当然了
Just maybe not today.
只是   可能不是今天
Alvin's right.
艾尔文说得对
-We should prepare to stay the night.-What? You guys expect me to sleep outside?
-我们得准备过夜 -什么   你们想要我在这睡   在野外
Last I checked, Brit, we are chipmunks.
这没什么   布列塔   我们是花栗鼠
-We are used to living in the wild.-No
-习惯生活在野外-不是
we used to be used to living in the wild.
我们曾经习惯生活在野外
Come on, Brit, it's just one night.
得了吧   布列塔   也就一个晚上
One cold night.
冰冷的夜晚